Let's expand on this list of steps that makes up our current funnel.
让我们在当前这个漏斗的步骤列表上进行补充
First, we could break up the step exploring the site.
首先 我们可以分解探索网站这个步骤
Exploring the site could mean that the student viewed a page listing
探索网站可能是指学员访问
all the classes that Audacity offers.
列出 Audacity 所有课程的网页
Or, it could mean that, from that list,
或者 可能指学员在这个列表上
the student clicked on an individual course to view more details about it.
点击一门课程 查看课程详情
Next, there are a lot of steps between creating an account and
其次 在创建帐户和
completing a class.
完成一门课程之间有很多步骤
First you could look at how many students start taking a class or
首先 你可以看看有多少学员开始学习一门课程
enroll in that class.
或选择这门课程
And since classes have several lessons,
由于一门课程由很多节课组成
you could keep track of progress through the class.
你可以跟踪这门课程的进度
How many users finish lesson one, lesson two, et cetera.
多少用户完成了第一课 多少用户完成了第二课等等
Audacity also provides coaching, so
Audacity 还提供辅导
during the lessons students can ask for help.
因此在课程期间学员可以求助
This is a paid service, so
这是一项收费服务
this is also how the business becomes financially sustainable.
这也确保了业务在财务上能够持续
There are different levels of coaching based on how much help the student
根据对学员需求帮助的程度 辅导分为几个等级
needs, so you could also track how many students use each level.
你还可以跟踪哪个等级有多少学员使用
After a student completes a course,
学员完成一门课程之后
you could go on to track whether that student enrolls in a second course.
你可以继续跟踪这名学员是否选择了第二门课程
And ultimately you want to know how many students get jobs with the help of
最终你想知道有多少学员在 Audacity 课程的帮助下找到了工作
Audacity classes, although this could be hard to measure.
虽然这可能很难衡量
Once we've made a list of potential steps,
在制定可能的步骤清单后
we can pick the most important ones, and use them to define a funnel.
我们可以选择最重要的一些步骤 并用其定义漏斗
In this case I've chosen the number of visits to the homepage,
在这里 我们选择主页访问量
the number of visits to the course list, the number of visits to each individual
课程清单访问量、各个课程页面访问量
course page, the number of accounts created.
创建的帐户数量
The number of enrollments and courses,
注册和课程人数
the number of students who used coaching,
选择辅导服务的学员数量
the number of students who complete a course, and the number of students who
完成课程的学员数量
go on to get a job as the steps that will make up our primary funnel.
和找到工作的学员数量 作为漏斗的主要组成部分
The reason this is called a funnel is that typically you have fewer and
将其称为漏斗是因为在漏斗中越处于下面的阶段
fewer users that get to each stage of the funnel.
用户数量越来越少
If you look at the actual timeline for a particular user,
如果你查看特定用户的实际时间线
though, it's more like a swirl.
就像是一个漩涡
For example,
例如
in this funnel, users might complete courses without accessing coaching.
在这个漏斗中 用户可能没有请求辅导就完成了课程
And students who haven't completed a course yet,
而未完成课程的学员
might return to enroll in a new course.
可能会返回注册一门新的课程
It's also important to consider how this funnel would look across different
想想这个漏斗如何适用于平台
platforms.
也很重要
Sometimes iPhone and Android apps have a slightly different flow
有时 iPhone 和 Android 应用在流程上有些差异
both from each other and from your desktop site.
其电脑版网页也有些不同
Although, in this case, these stages should be supported on all platforms.
虽然 在这个例子中 所有平台都应支持这些步骤
You also need to be able to track progress through the funnel across
你还需要能够跨越各个平台
platforms.
跟踪漏斗的进程
For example, you might see that people start the class on their phone,
例如 有时候用户一开始可能在手机上参加课程
then continue it on their laptop.
后来在笔记本电脑上继续学习
Each stage in the funnel right now is a metric that you could use for
现在漏斗的各个阶段都是你可以用于实验的一个指标
an experiment, the number of users who reach that point in the funnel.
到达漏斗这个点的用户数量
This type of metric is called a count.
这类指标称为计数指标
However, sometimes instead of a count, you'll want to use a rate or
但有时 你不想使用计数指标
a probability like you saw in lesson one.
而想使用你在第一课中看到的一个比率或概率
Often, you'll want to keep the counts at a few key points in the funnel.
一般情况下 你想对漏斗中的一些关键点进行计数
For example, the number of people who visit the homepage and
例如 访问主页的人数
the number of people who enroll in courses.
和注册课程的人数
For other points in the funnel,
对于漏斗中的其他点
you might want to switch to a rate by dividing the number of
你可能想通过
users at that level of the funnel by the number at the previous level.
这一等级上的用户数量除以上一等级的人数 来转化成一个比率
For example, instead of measuring the number of users
例如 不测量访问课程列表的用户数量
who visit the course list, you might measure the rate at which people
而是测量从查看概览页面到课程列表页面
progress from viewing the overview page to the list of courses.
的人数的比率
Since people move between these two levels of the funnel using
因为使用“现在开始”按钮人们可以在漏斗的这两个等级间移动
the Start Now button, this is the same as the click-through
这和我们在第一课中谈到的
rate of the Start Now button that we discussed in lesson one.
“现在开始”按钮的点击率一样
The reason to use a rate is because you want to first figure out how many people
使用比率是因为你想先计算出有多少人
enter the funnel.
进入到这个漏斗中了
And then increase the rate at which people progress down the funnel.
然后提高人们进入漏斗下一层的比率
For each rate in the funnel, you might also care about the probability that
对于漏斗中的每个比率 你可能也会关心
a unique user progresses down the funnel.
一个用户深入到这个漏斗下层的概率是多少
For viewing the list of courses, you probably care about how
对于查看课程列表 你可能关心
easy it is to do this from the Course Overview page, which is all right.
从课程概述页面查看课程列表有多容易 这个还好
But you probably also care about whether a student reached
但你可能还关心一名学员是否接触到了课程列表
the course list at all, which is a binary probability.
这是一个二元概率
Now for all of these metrics, they're not yet metrics you could actually use.
现在 所有这些指标都不是你能够实际使用的指标
We start with these high level concepts.
我们从这些高级概念开始
What business objective you're tracking through the funnel,
你在漏斗中跟踪的业务目标是什么
whether you care about the absolute number or the count, the usability, or
你关心绝对数、计数、易用性
the rate, or the progression, the probability.
比率、进展还是概率
But, we still have to transform these into full definitions.
但是我们必须将这些转化为完整的定义
Before we tackle that though, we're first going to go into some
在转化之前 我们首先要看看
other techniques for coming up with these high level concept metrics.
提出这些高级概念指标的一些其他技术